Contact

jaimietropin@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jaimie-grayo-banks-msn-cmsrn-cbn-fnp-cb75507b9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Nursing Hospitals

Jaimie Gray-O'Banks MSN CMSRN CBN FNP-C

Bariatric Nurse Practitioner at Crystal Run Healthcare Greater New York City Area

Summary

Experienced Family Nurse Practitioner with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Patient Safety, Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, and Inpatient/Outpatient Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science (MS) focused in Family Nurse Practitioner from Mount Saint Mary College.

Experience

Crystal Run Health 4 years 11 months

Family Nurse Practitioner October 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months) Middletown, NY

Bariatric nurse practitioner

Family Nurse Practitioner August 2015 - September 2017 (2 years 2 months) Rock Hill, NY

Internal Medicine

Orange Regional Medical Center Registered Nurse

Education

Mount Saint Mary College

Master of Science (MS), Family Nurse Practitioner · (2010 - 2015)

Mount Saint Mary College

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2004 - 2008)